IL Cafe we have you
covered hello and welcome to Il Cafe my
name is shidel and today we have an
episode that's going to dwell on this
phrase that captures a lot of
imaginations and for the right reasons
because it is indeed uh an effort to
empower customers anywhere cashless and
I've decided to figure out what this new
offering from the ICS Lombard universe
is all about it's a new innovation
indeed for health insurance policy
holders and to help understand its
benefits a little bit better I've got
with me an expert from the ICI Lombard
family and that is shelish Du shales
thank you so much for joining us and
welcome to the show oh thank you thank
you sh and indeed it's my pleasure to
join the your show and uh give my input
on that yeah let's quickly get started
with the definition right would be
useful for our viewers to understand
exactly what you mean by anywhere
cashless and how it is how is it
different from the other different you
know health insurance offerings
certainly sh anywhere cash is a facility
under the policy where the policy holder
of ICC Lombard can take a treatment in
any hospital at pan India level so uh in
short uh now there is a no restriction
of hos Network hospital for taking a
treatment a customer can go to anywhere
in India and he or she can off for
cashless treatment in any hospital so
this is a unique feature of anywhere
cashless Okay so What specifically what
benefits uh shell does anyway cashless
offer to policy holders in terms of the
choice of hospital and also the
convenience or ease of uh you know
operating this if you talk about the
benefit there is no limitation of
hospital now customer can go to any
Hospital uh whether whether it is nearby
to their house or irrespective of any
speciality of the hospital so it's like
a paradigm shift in the entire Insurance
business uh where customer can get to
only hospital and take a treatment so
this is a unique feature of anyway
cashless now uh how does this particular
you know Innovation anyway catless
eliminate the worries that are
associated with some of the upfront
payments that need to be made during
hospitalization in Shades if you see the
pictures of anywhere cashless or the
cash list is like customer need not to
pay anything from their pocket so in in
the cash list facility customer can get
into the hospital take a treatment and
at a time of discharge they need not to
worry about the money
everything is is handled by the
insurance company so this is a payment
part where customer need not to worry
about anything paying from their pocket
mhm and what about the other side the
claims you know part Etc because I'm
sure there are hassles along the entire
chain of events that people normally you
know face so how does this really
anywhere cashless help the entire
process okay so uh actually what
happened in anywhere cash the customer
can skip the cumbersome process of
submitting your document and waiting for
for their claim approval and getting for
their money from the insurance company
so with this anywhere cashless uh entire
this traditional way of claim submission
like sending their physical document to
the insurance company and following up
with the insurance company for their
payment it it will get eliminated with
the with the features of anywhere cash
list now in anywhere cash list customer
need to go to the hospital they need to
uh they need to inform to the insurance
company to the ICC Lombard and post that
everything will be taken care by the ICC
Lombard uh so customer need not to worry
about anything apart from that yeah just
needs to focus on getting better right
if you're inde the customer who availing
the service yourself uh but yeah this
places usually in other situations right
a lot of strain on somebody's U state of
uh wellbe because a you are in the
situation B then you have to an entire
human being from the family has to be
deployed for
just tasks right and you to
say type of can you know go to school
and do what the has to do a college or
whatever and uh clearly that's what I'm
hearing from you now what are the steps
if you could break down the steps for
our viewers in terms of policy holders
availing of the N calist Service uh what
are the things they need to remember
okay so there is some Elementary uh
condition like for availing anywhere
cashless facility the first customer
need to inform to ICC Lombard within uh
prior to 24h hour first pration that is
a condition number one for availing a
cashless anywhere cash uh customer can
go to our app Al take care app uh there
is a section called Health assistance
where they can go and they can opt for
anywhere cashless option over there
after opting the option then the person
from Lombard will connect with the
customer or connect with the hospital to
arranging the cash L to the customer so
this is a basic simple step which
customer need to follow and uh after
getting intimation at our in from the
customer side uh everything will be
taken care from ICC and after following
with the hospital and after having a
word with the customer for arranging the
cash L now to come to the benefits like
long-term benefits I usually ask this
question only from the point of view of
you know policy holders but I'm going to
twist that around a little bit and I
want to know what's in it for IC lumbar
also why would something like Anyway
cist help an organization that offers
the service and also the policy holders
who available yeah so for the
organization if you see somewhere uh we
want to serve our customer and we want
to provide a quality services to our
customer and uh based on our analysis
and Survey so what we found out most of
the customer they are they are referring
to the hospital of their choice so with
the help of anywhere cashless now we can
provide a uh choice of Hospital of the
customer and as a organization we are
getting a uh intimation from the
customer side and uh based on that uh we
can we can enhance our services in the
hospital and we can we can ask the
hospital to provide a best best care to
our customer so if you talk about the
organization in organization in long
term uh the customer satisfaction is the
one of the most important uh factor
which organization will get from this uh
facility any final words shales um in
closing any advice perhaps that you'd
like to give to anyone who's considering
ICC Lombard complete health insurance
and the anywhere cashless feature it
offers yeah so my only advice to
everyone who who's looking into the IC
Lombard health insurance policy they
need to think about the facility of
anywhere cashless because it's a very
very unique features which is offered by
asenti Lombard and uh somewhere customer
is going to get a lot of benefit from
this feature with a advice to the
customer ke if they want to utilize this
Services they need to inform to the
insurance company within 24 hours prior
to their hospitalization and uh as
organization we want this facility to be
popularized uh in the market and
customer can use this facility at a best
m
interesting thank you so much for all
these pointers with respect to this
groundbreaking Innovation that icsu
Lombard offers to people who are looking
at their own health and securing Peace
of Mind in that journey and here's
wishing all of you a very very good uh
you know sort of rest of the remaining
months of the year 2023 and uh continued
good health indeed and before you sign
out ches out of syllabus golya question
coming up for you since we talking about
anywhere cash list that phrase is like
you know suddenly in my mind because I
realized a lot of Life generally is
happening cashless only nowadays do you
remember going anywhere suddenly saying
that by it's a good thing that life is
cashless for me it was U you know when I
wanted to buy suddenly there was Peru
you know what we call Amud or in
Gujarati we call it jam and suddenly I
saw this and 10 bucks I have 10 bucks in
my wallet to give to somebody and I was
like Google pay here and this happened
when was the last personal experience
that you had using some of these digital
payments when you least expected that
you might have to use it I can I can say
that digital payment is a revolution in
the entire payment journey and and and
it's giving a lot of benefit to all the
all the user not only me but all the
citizen of India and uh coming to your
point I'm using uh digital payment very
very frequently so it is not just only
for purchasing Peru or something like
that yeah absolutely that was just an
example but you know that is somehow it
gives you MTI in your head saying that
oh is also possible for 10 10 Rupees you
can actually use digital payments but
yeah the only reason I brought this
unrelated kind of you know area over
here because at anywhere cashless is how
I go outside the house also cashless
sometimes but nice to have spoken of it
in the context of insurance offerings at
ICS chish thank you so much for your
time and here's wishing you the best of
health as well you're most welcome and
thanks for my site